<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<banks_list>
    <bank>
        <name>ICBC</name>
        <founding_date>1984</founding_date>
        <description>
            <capital>
                339
                <capital_unit>
                    billion of dollars
                </capital_unit>
            </capital>
            <workers_amount>453048</workers_amount>
            <headquarters>
                <country>
                    China
                    <city>
                        Beijing
                    </city>
                </country>
            </headquarters>
            <history>
                As of 2006, ICBC has 2.5 million corporate customers and 150 million individual customers. In 2005, net
                profit was up 12.4% to RMB 33.7 billion, and the total loan balance was RMB 3,289.5 billion. Total
                liabilities are RMB 6,196.2 billion, up 11.2%. Delinquent or non-performing loans (NPL) total RMB 154.4
                billion, a significant reduction although the figures are widely regarded as being somewhat higher than
                officially stated. It has an NPL ratio of 4.69% and a capital adequacy ratio of 9.89%.

                As of December 2, 2014, ICBC is ranked the largest bank in the world by assets and by tier 1 capital. In
                July 2007 it was ranked 30th in the world in terms of revenue.
            </history>
            <awards>
                <award>Best Banking Performer, China in 2016 by Global Brands Magazine Award</award>
                <award>Global 2000 Rank #1 - World's Largest Public Companies in 2016</award>
                <award>List of Awards to ICBC in 2016</award>
            </awards>
        </description>
    </bank>
    <bank>
        <name>CCB</name>
        <founding_date>1954</founding_date>
        <description>
            <capital>
                290
                <capital_unit>
                    billion of dollars
                </capital_unit>
            </capital>
            <workers_amount>345971</workers_amount>
            <headquarters>
                <country>
                    China
                    <city>
                        Beijing
                    </city>
                </country>
            </headquarters>
            <history>
                CCB was founded on 1 October 1954 under the name of People's Construction Bank of China and later
                changed to China Construction Bank on 26
                March 1996.

                In January 2002, CCB Chairman Wang Xuebing resigned from the bank after being charged with accepting
                bribes while he was employed with Bank of China; he was sentenced to 12 years in prison. In March 2005,
                his successor, Zhang Enzhao, resigned for "personal reasons". Just prior to his resignation, he had been
                charged in a lawsuit with accepting a US$1 million bribe. He was later sentenced to 15 years in jail in
                connection with the case.

                China Construction Bank Corporation was formed as a joint-stock commercial bank in September 2004 as a
                result of a separation procedure undertaken by its predecessor, China Construction Bank, under the PRC
                Company Law. Following the China Banking Regulatory Committee's approval on 14 September 2004, the next
                day the bank (Jianyin) became a separate legal entity, owned by the Chinese government holding company,
                Central Huijin Investment Company or simply Huijin.

                During the 2013 Korean crisis, the China Construction Bank halted business with a North Korean bank
                accused by the United States of financing Pyongyang's missile and nuclear programs.

                In 2015, China Construction Bank ranks the 2nd in Forbes’ 13th annual Global 2000 ranking of the
                biggest, most powerful and most valuable companies in the world.
            </history>
            <awards>
                <award>Global 2000 Rank #2 - World's Largest Public Companies in 2016</award>
            </awards>
        </description>
    </bank>
</banks_list>